The Nintendo Switch.
任天堂Switch
Mine’s had a rough few days, and the violence isn’t over just yet.
我的已经被怼了好几天了，但还远远不够。
It’s time to take it apart and review the Switch from the inside.
是时候拆解它来看看内部构造了。
Remember, don’t ever attempt this on your own device unless it’s totally broken and
记住别试图用你自己的设备来实验，除非它完全坏了
you have no other options.
而你别无选择。
I’ll be linking all available repair parts in the video description, just let me know
在视频简介中我会给出可维修部件的视频链接，如果你有特殊需求
if you need something specific.
请让我知道。
Let’s get started.
开始吧。
For the past few consoles, Nintendo has been using their own proprietary tri-point screw
在过去的一些控制器中，任天堂在后背板一直使用他们自家的三点螺钉
on the back panel and the Switch is no exception.
所以这台Switch也毫不例外。
Four tri-point screws along the back side and 5 Philips head screws along the side rail.
背部有四个三点螺丝而侧边则有5个十字槽头螺丝。
And then the metal joy-con rail can detach from the console, but be careful with it and
然后可以把侧边的无线手柄从主机中拆下来
don’t pull it off completely just yet.
但是要小心别完全的把它拆下来。
I’ll show you why in just a second.
我会在接下来告诉你为什么。
The bottom has two screws; also Phillips head.
底部有两个螺丝，都是十字口的。
And the two little circles next to the screws are guiding posts for the USBC port inside
螺钉旁边的两个小圆圈是端口坞内的USB-C接口的引导柱
of the dock; super smart because that will put less stress on the charging port when
十分聪明的设计，当充电时，会减少对充电接口的压力
it’s docked; helping it last longer.
让它使用更长时间。
Now I accidentally snapped my other joy-con rail off the console in my last video, but
在上一个视频中，我意外地将无线手柄的导轨取出
normally this would have 5 screws holding it in place as well.
但通常它会有5个螺丝来固定。
Just pretend they’re there.
所以就假装那些螺丝还在那里吧。
Lastly, one screw along the top next to the heat vent.
最后，还有一个螺丝在顶部的散热孔旁边
The cooling system on this thing is actually pretty sweet.
这个冷却系统实在是酷毙了。
I’ll show you more of that once we get inside.
一旦进去了，你就能感受到更多。
The kickstand is covering the last little screw, and once that’s removed the whole
最后一个小螺丝被支架覆盖住了，只要取出了它
back panel can be pulled off the Nintendo Switch console.
整个后背板就可以拿出来了。
Interesting that this particular device has never been opened before, yet there are fingerprints
有趣的是这个设备以前从未被拆过
all over the place.
可指纹却到时都是
Really not that important, but it is interesting to see a human had to assemble this at some point.
这个不大重要，但有趣的是可以看出有人在某些地方组装的痕迹。
The SD card tray that is hidden by the kickstand is here and is 100 percent modular with one
SD卡槽藏在支架的下面，肯定用一个螺丝固定着
screw holding it in and the same Lego-like connection you’ve seen on pretty much every cell phone.
就像在手机上经常看见的那种乐高式的连接
There are 6 more normal Phillips head screws along the inside of this back metal panel.
在这个金属板的内部，有6个额外的十字口螺丝
Then you can remove the metal plate from the consol.
然后你能从主机上拆下这块金属板。
Now this metal plate is interesting on two levels: one, it’s got a series of phone
这个金属背板有两个有趣的地方：
pads along the back to keep the separation from the circuits, and to keep vibrations to a minimum,
一是它采用类似手机、平板那套方式来划分电路的走向，以将振动达到最小。
and it’s also got the largest glob of thermal paste that I’ve ever seen
二是它用了一坨大得罕见的硅胶
inside of mobile unit.
涂在移动单元上
But it makes sense when we finally get to look at the size of this heat pipe.
不过当我们看到这个导热管的大小时就觉得它是很有意义的
This heat pipe is used to wick away heat from the main processor which is the hottest and
这个热导管用来带走主处理器产生的热量
hardest working component inside any computer or gaming system like this.
这在任何电脑、游戏系统中都是发热最多、功耗最大的地方。
So the heat goes in two directions; the first is through the large glob of thermal paste,
所以这个热量主要有两个导向：一是通过那团导热硅胶
right into the large silver metal backing.
导向那个背部银色金属板。
And the second is through the copper heat pipe along the fan and spitting out the top
二则是通过那个导热铜管导向设备顶部的
of the device.
散热风扇
I’ll remove that heat pipe and look at that in just a second.
接下来我会拆解这个导热铜管看看。
I’ll disconnect the battery first, which is smart practice anytime you work on anything electronic.
我首先会先拆下电池，这是你在拆解任何电子时最好的做法。
I did warm up the screen for a second to try and soften the super strong adhesive under
我需要花一小会吹热吹软粘连屏幕和电池中的大力胶
the battery, since this will probably be repair people will want to attempt in a few years
只要当这个电池能被更换被修复，人们就会在几年内开始尝试(拆电池)
when their own batteries start dying.
当他们的电池开始老化。
This is normally not good for the battery and is actually pretty dangerous if you use
这对电池不好，并且非常危险当你使用
a metal tool.
一个金属工具
I wish Nintendo would have used the magic adhesive pull tabs that we see in most cell
希望任天堂能像现在大部分的智能手机那样
phones these days.
使用神奇的粘性金属拉环。
These pull tabs cost pennies to manufacture and they make repairs so much easier and safer
金属拉片大规模生产成本低，并能让像我这样维修小子
for repair guys like myself.
维修时容易安全得多。
Maybe next time, Nintendo?
下一次吧，任天堂？
The battery has a pretty large capacity at 4300 milliamp hours.
这电池有4300毫安的大容量。
Remember how I said earlier to be gentle with these side rails?
记得我之前说过的要温柔地拆开侧边导轨了吗？
There’s a small ribbon cable that goes to the main board, and this is what will be charging
这里有一个小带状导线连接主板，是用来
your joy-con controller.
给你的无线手柄充电的。
So if this breaks, so does the charger to your controller and, you know, the controllers
所以如果这个坏了的话，你的手柄就充不了电
are kind of important.
你知道的，手柄还是很重要的。
There are dual speakers at the bottom of the game system.
有两个扬声器在游戏机的底部。
These fire out through the holes below the front screen.
声音通过屏幕下方的小孔出去。
And the USBC port is here in the center, soldered onto the main board.
USB-C接口在这中间，焊接在主面板上面
Keeping your screws organized, there are three more over here.
让你的螺丝井然有序，这儿还有3个。
I’m pulling out the game cartridge slot and the headphone jack; they are on the same circuit board.
我正拔出游戏卡槽和耳机孔，他们被焊接在同一个电路板上。
There’s a large ribbon cable attached to the top.
顶部有一根大型带状导线。
Each ribbon connector has a locking latch that lifts up to unlock, and then the ribbon
每一根带状线都有一个插槽锁定装置，向上提的话它就会解锁
cable can slide out.
然后带状线就会滑出来了。
Then the board also has a Lego-type connector under the heat pipe that unsnaps.
主板也有一个乐高类型的插槽，在导热铜线的下面,很容易取走。
This thing looks pretty sweet, and now you know if multiple games stop being read by
这个看起来很温馨，现在你应该知道如果几个游戏在你的游戏机中读取不了时
your console, this guy’s probably the culprit and needs to be replaced.
这家伙很有可能是罪魁祸首，应该被替换
If all else fails, you might be able to digitally download your games to the consol.
如果一切都失败了，你可能需要重新下载这个游戏到底游戏机里。
This is what I did with the Zelda game that I’m currently playing.
我正在玩的塞尔达传说就是这样的情况。
Let’s get rid of some more screws.
让我们来卸下更多螺丝。
There are 3 screws holding down the copper heat pipe, just over the processor.
这儿有3个螺丝固定着导热管，就在处理机上
Try to keep the thermal paste intact cuz as long as it’s not dry and crusty you can
试着保持硅胶的完好无损，因为只要他没有干掉而且结成块，
probably just reuse it.
你就能重新使用它
If it’s all dried up, you can probably just reapply some normal thermal paste that you
如果它完全的干掉了，你可以重新够买一些并涂上去，
can find on Amazon.
能在亚马逊上找到。
I’ll try to link some in the video description.
我尽力链接一些在视频的简介中。
There’s a bunch more screws holding the main board into place.
还有许多螺丝固定着主板。
Remember to keep these organized.
注意要保持井然有序。
Your life will be easier if you do.
这样会很方便。
The other joy-con rail is plugged into this side of the motherboard.
另一个无线手柄导轨插在主板的这边。
Unlatch the lock and the ribbon can slide out.
拉开锁带状导线就能滑出。
The speakers can be found in the bottom corners of the Nintendo Switch, and the interesting
扬声器在游戏机的底部角落。
thing is is that the speaker cone is made from the same rubber material that we saw
有趣的是，这扬声器的锥型震膜所使用的橡胶材质
inside the Apple Airpods.
与苹果的Airpods相同。
So while the Nintendo Switch itself is not waterproof, if any liquid accidentally falls
所以，由于Switch它本身并不防水，如果有任何液体意外掉落
into the speaker slots, the speakers themselves can’t survive.
扬声器便会宣告GG。
Nintendo did use quality speaker material.
不过老任在扬声器上确实使用了优质的材料。
The water damage indicator is right here next to the corner of the battery.
水损指示器就在这里，在电池旁的一角。
And then we release the large ribbon that sits right below where the cartridge used to be.
然后我们把位于游戏卡槽正下方的大带状导线移除。
And finally, the beastly heat pipe can be removed.
最后，我们可以拆掉这个可恶的导热管。
This helps wick heat away from the processor.
这有助于让核心热量远离处理器。
Without this, the system might overheat and turn off.
否则，系统可能会因过热而关闭。
If you remember, I use a thermal imaging camera on my LG G6 teardown to see if the heat pipes
也许你还记得，我曾经在我的LG G6拆机上使用热成像摄像机看看热管实际上是否工作，
actually work, and they do.
它们确实工作了
And this heat pipe is even bigger than the ones we’ve seen inside of other smart phones.
这个热管甚至比那些我所见过的智能手机里面的还要大。
It’s even got fins up at the top to let the air flow through and let it cool down
它甚至在顶部有散热片，可以让空气流过，让它冷却得
faster.
更快。
Just a few more things to unplug like the volume and power ribbon, and the fan ribbon.
还要多拔几个零件，比如音量控制、电源、风扇的带状导线。
I’ll show you more on these in just a second.
我马上向你展示更多。
One more wire cable on the left side, and then this little guy right here is extremely
在左边还有一根电线
interesting.
这个小家伙在这里非常有趣。
This is the build in memory for the device, and it looks like it’s replaceable.
这是设备的内存构建，看上去这个是可以替换的。
Normally phones and tablets have their memory soldered directly onto the main board.
通常手机和平板电脑的内存都是直接焊接在主板上。
And it looks like this system might be able to upgrade and hold more memory in the future.
看起来这个系统在将来也许能够升级，并有更多的内存。
It’ll be easy for Nintendo to start selling larger capacity switches because none of the
对任天堂来说，开始售卖更大容量switches是很简单的事，
board schematics would have to change if the memory is swappable like this.
因为如果内存像这样可以替换，就不需要改变任何一个电路板原理图。
Just plug the new memory in and you’re good to go.
只是插入新的内存，这很简单。
Finally, here is the main board, the brains of the device.
最后，这里是主板，机子的大脑核心。
The charging port is directly soldered in place and not replaceable, unfortunately.
不幸的是。充电端口直接焊接到位，不可更换。
But I imagine that the dock is pretty sturdy, so wear and tear on the port should be minimal,
但我认为，端口坞是很坚固的，所以端口的磨损应该是很小的
but even then, it would be nice to see a replaceable charging port like we have on most cell phones these days.
即便如此，可替换充电端口会更棒，像现在我们大多数手机上的那样。
The last thing to come out of the frame is the fan with its three screws.
最后从框架出来的，是用三个螺丝固定的风扇。
This fan, coupled with the large copper heat pipe and heat sink, should do a pretty good
这个风扇，加上大铜热管和散热器，可以形成一个很好的平衡，保持凉爽。
job of keeping the tablet cool, especially since it’s only running at 720p when it’s
特别是因为它只运行720P游戏时
not docked.
没有卡顿。
The super long ribbon cable at the top is for the volume and power buttons.
顶部的超长带状电缆用于音量和电源按钮。
And then there is this last joy-con rail on the side that we unplugged earlier.
然后，这里是最后的手柄导轨，我们之前拔出的那个。
Now the screen.
现在，屏幕。
The exterior plastic layer and the LCD layer are not glued to each other like we see on
外部塑料层和LCD层并没有胶合
most cell phones.
像大部分智能手机那样
They are actually independent components; like on an iPad.
它们实际上是独立的组件，就像iPad上一样。
But they are glued to the consol itself.
但是它们被粘到了游戏机本身上。
It has not been easy to find replacement parts for Nintendo products in the past, but if
过去很难找到任天堂产品的替换零件，
I do find replacement screens, they will be linked in the video description.
但我确实找到了可替换的屏幕，我会把他们的链接放在视频说明里。
You’ll need to use heat to separate the screen from the frame, and then the new screen
你需要通过加热将屏幕与框架分开，
will have it’s own adhesive.
然后新的屏幕将有它自己的胶粘剂。
I personally want to play Zelda later though, so I’m going to leave my screen intact for now.
我之后想要玩塞尔达传说，所以现在要保持屏幕的完好
It’s time to reassemble this thing and see if it still works when I put it back together.
是时候重新组装这家伙了，看看是否还能工作，当我将它们重组时。
Putting it back together should be easier than taking it apart if you kept your screws
组装这家伙比拆它应该容易些，
organized.
如果你没有把螺丝丢掉的话。
Fan goes in first, then the motherboard gets set into place; charging port in first, making
风扇先进入，然后主板就位; 充电口先来，
sure no ribbons or wires are stuck under the board when you set it down into the frame.
当你把它放入框架的时候，确保没有丝带或电线被卡在板下面。
Everything has it’s own slot to slide into, like the speakers.
所有东西都有它自己的插槽去插入，就像扬声器一样。
I’ll get the fan ribbon cable tucked into the slot, and the volume ribbon tucked into
我会把风扇的带状导线塞进插槽，音量控制的的带状导线塞进它的插槽;
it’s slot; and make sure that they are both locked down with their little latches.
插好了，并确定它们全都固定好。
The larger ribbon is the same deal; slip it in and lock it down.
大带子也是一样; 滑入并扣好。
Then the cartridge and headphone jack board can get plugged in with the little Lego-like
然后，游戏卡槽和耳机接口板可以插入到小的乐高式连接口;
connector; you’ll feel it click into place.
你会感觉到它插入到位。
And the heat pipe gets set down, grill side first.
然后导热管从侧面放入。
And three screws hold it snug against the processor.
然后三个螺丝让它紧贴处理器。
Remember if your thermal paste is super crusty, you might want to glob some new stuff on if
记住，如果你的散热膏是超硬的，你可能需要一些挤新的
your consol is overheating or something.
如果你的游戏机过热或不正常。
Joy-con rails get put into place and latched down.
无线手柄导轨顺着位置插入锁定。
Make sure that it has a good connection before latching it into place.
确保在将它锁定到位之前已经连接好。
The ribbon cable that gets plugged into the cartridge gets slipped in and latched down.
把游戏卡槽的带状电缆插入并锁定。
And then the other joy-con rail gets lined up along the side and the two ribbon cables
然后另一个手柄导轨沿着底部扬声器的两条带状电缆塞进到位
near the bottom speaker get tucked into place and latched down like the rest of them.
并且像其他一样锁住
Set down the black plastic bracket over the headphone jack and then we can set the 4300
将黑色塑料支架放在耳机插孔上，
milliamp battery back into place and plug it in.
然后我们可以将4300毫安电池放回原位，然后插入。
I’m just reusing the same adhesive as before, but if you buy a new battery it will probably
我只是重复使用与以前相同的粘合剂，但如果你买一个新的电池
come with it’s own adhesive.
它可能会附带有自己的粘合剂。
Get the rest of your motherboard screws into place.
把其余的主板螺丝固定到位。
Assuming you had this all organized, this should be relatively easy.
假设你之前有条理地整理螺丝，这相对来说比较容易。
Another interesting thing is that this black tape on the metal backing.
另一个有趣的事情是，这个黑色的胶带在金属背衬上。
This is a super cheap way to keep the silver from shining through the little grill slots
这是一个超级便宜的方式，
on the back of the consol.
通过在控制台背面的小烧烤槽保持银发光。
Pretty cost effective way to keep the controller looking clean and blacked out.
相当经济而有效的方式，可以让游戏机看起来干净发亮。
And a final screw next to the SD card slot.
最后一个螺丝位于SD卡插槽旁边。
After you finish plugging that into the main board like a little Lego, then affix the foam
在像玩乐高一样插入主板后，
pad over the connector.
将泡沫垫贴在连接器上。
The foam pad will help it keep from accidentally disconnecting if it’s ever dropped.
泡沫垫将有助于防止它意外断开，如果它掉下来过。
The back plastics can fall into place at this point, with one screw at the top of the consol,
背面塑料可以在该点放到位，其中一个螺钉在设备的顶部，
two more screws at the bottom, and 5 screws on either side of the device.
两个螺钉在底部，并且在设备的任一侧上都有5个螺钉。
All of these are your normal Philips head screws.
这些都是正常十字形螺丝。
And lastly, 4 screws along the back, with the little guy underneath the kickstand as well.
最后，4个螺丝沿着后面，有小家伙也在支架下面。
And it looks like everything works.
它看起来一切正常。
I can keep playing Zelda now, at least until I take apart the joy-con controllers to see
我可以继续玩塞尔达传说，至少在我拆开手柄前，
how they work.
看看他们如何工作。
This poor system has been through quite a lot and it keeps on chugging.
这个可怜系统已经经过了相当多的时间，并且它一直在蜷缩。
I’m pretty impressed.
我印象非常深刻。
My Instagram followers got to watch me stream this teardown live on Instagram.
我的Ins粉丝直播看我的拆解流程。
We just hung out and talked for about an hour as I took this thing apart for the video.
我们刚刚出去，并谈了大约一个小时，关于我把这个东西分开的视频。
Follow me over there if you want to jump in and chat during the next teardown.
在那里关注我，如果你想在下一次拆卸时加入聊天。
翻译：@不轻 @深涧游鱼乐不知
校对：@95uxin
Thanks a ton for watching.
肥肠感谢观看。
I’ll see you around!
回头见！